[{"answer": "I think it is.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Is it going too far?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "I think there have been more unforced errors than you would expect from a presidential campaign in the final months.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "How significant are these alleged gaffes be?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "You have just got to assume, when you're in a presidential race, that every single moment is on the record.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "When Bill Clinton was fundraising, for example, would he often go harder on the rhetoric, thinking he was in a secure room with people that he could trust, or is this Mitt Romney's big fatal flaw, that he's been caught talking in a different way?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well -- if you look back at that primary field that we were dealing with a year ago, watching in debates a year ago, there's no question with the exception perhaps of Rick Perry, who ended up imploding for other reasons, I don't think there was anybody else on that stage who could have gotten the nomination and been competitive in a presidential race.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "If they had somebody like that, would they be doing better in the polls?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "You got nothing left to lose.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "What do you say to him?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "You know, the transplant went as well, it's transfusion, really, went as well as can be expected.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "How is she doing, do you know?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "No, I think what he was earlier saying is that the president was polling at 47 percent, still is.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "I mean what's going on here?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Two things.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "You must have been incandescent, were you?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Well, I think you're going to have to increase taxes, Piers, on people who are very fortunate in this society, who are very wealthy.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Can you do it without increasing any taxation, because from where I sit, I just don't see that is a feasible position?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, he needs to keep saying what he has been saying and force the press to focus on that.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "What has he got to do to refocus, to re-galvanize and to try and get the right message over now to win this election?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I don't think there's very much merit, if any merit at all, Piers.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Robert Reich, is there merit to what Grover Norquist is saying there?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "You must be worried, aren't you?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "The Soviet Union was no more of a financial burden on America than Afghanistan and Iraq had been.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Can I just -- can I just intervene here?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "The fact of the matter is the Reagan recession was very deep, but it is nothing compared to what Barack Obama inherited from George W. Bush.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "That's civil?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, if you look at --", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Has any president in the history of the United States ever handed a bigger financial crisis over to the guy that followed him than George Bush did?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Herbert Hoover.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, he did -- Hoover took tax rates up to 75 percent from 25.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Are you saying that FDR was the same as Herbert Hoover?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "It's not, because the president just gave a speech about how the American people demanded Obamacare.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Isn't that a very similar position to what we're now seeing?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Not much of it good.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "As to that part of it, plenty.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "How much credence should we be giving it, do you think?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "No, he was in custody of the Defense Department.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "I wouldn't even have been aware of him being released?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, it's essentially a franchise.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "It is just a collection of terrorist cells around the world?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Sure, it's plausible.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Do you think that is plausible?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "UKASEY: I don't take a denial from the Justice Department as dispositive.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Do you think there's any danger that he will be released at any stage, in any capacity?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "America has always been under attack from al Qaeda.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Final point I would make, do you believe from what we have seen in the last week, then, that America is once again under attack from al Qaeda?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "ICARD: Well, we'd like to think that we can recover all the 17.5 billion dollars.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "I suppose the obvious question is how much can we expect to recover in the end?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "It depends on litigation.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Is that likely?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely, because we started at zero.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Are you pleasantly encouraged by how far you've come so far?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "I would say no.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Stephen, has Bernie Madoff been helpful at all in this process?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "ICARD: I really haven't thought about characterizing him at this point, because our efforts and our focus has been to go out and recover what we can, as much as we can, as quickly as we can, for the people for whom we are trying to get the best recoveries and best distribution.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "How would you categorize him?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "This was the biggest Ponzi scheme in American history, right?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "If you were to succeed in recovering the money, it would be the biggest recovery of its type that we would have ever seen?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I don't know that I would go that far, because, you know --", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "He's pretty despicable human being, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, that is true.", "docId": "120920pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Is that the maxim?", "qSentId": 569}]